

Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: <a href="mailto:consultant@londonresearchinternational.com">consultant@londonresearchinternational.com</a> www.LondonResearchInternational.com

# Mr. Maxwell

**NATIONALITY**: Nigeria

## **SUMMARY**

Mr. Maxwell is an experienced consultant, research analyst, and economist in the following areas:

- Financial strategy
- Financial modeling
- o Public relations/communications
- Business analysis
- Development competencies

His experienced countries are Nigeria, South Africa, Kenya, Angola and Ghana.

#### **EDUCATION**

- Bayero University Kano, 1995-2000, BSc Economics
- Bayero University Kano, 2004-2005, MSc Banking and Finance

### **EMPLOYMENT RECORD**

- Oldstone & Green Ltd (Jan 2011 present/ Nigeria): Consulting partner
  Oldstone & Green Ltd is a client focused strategy consulting, research and advisory firm, working with private firms, the public sector and donor organisations in our specialist practice areas.
- Zenith International (Dec 2012 Sept 2013/ United Kingdom): Country Associate
  Zenith International London is a leading international consultancy that advises the food and drink industry on business and technical issues ranging from international business strategy to factory design. Zenith works with over 1000 clients, in more than



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com

www.LondonResearchInternational.com

90 countries. As Country Associate, I manage projects and analyst in 5 African Countries – Nigeria, South Africa, Kenya, Angola and Ghana.

- Euromonitor International (March 2010 present/ United Kingdom): Independent
  In-Country Research Analyst
- ERGO ( Jan 2013 present/Nigeria): In-Country Consultant
- Gerson Lehrman Group (Jan 2012 present/ Nigeria): Consultant
- Euromoney Country Risk ( Jan 2011 present/Nigeria) : Country Economist
- Nova Capital Partners (Feb 2011 Feb 2013/ New York): Principal
- HORD Consulting (Dec 2010 Dec 2011/ Nigeria): Independent Management
  Consultant

Other work experiences are as senior research analyst, writer, and marketing executive since 2002.

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Oldstone & Green Ltd (Jan 2011 – present/ Nigeria): Consulting partner

Oldstone & Green Ltd is a client focused strategy consulting, research and advisory firm, working with private firms, the public sector and donor organisations in our specialist practice areas. Our key areas are:

- o Research & Advisory Service
- o Competitive Intelligence
- o Competitive Analysis
- o Competitor Analysis
- o Market Intelligence
- o Risk Management
- o Environment, Social Governance (ESG) Sustainability

Zenith International (Dec 2012 – Sept 2013/ United Kingdom): Country Associate

Zenith International London is a leading international consultancy that advises the



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

 $\label{lemail:consultant@londonresearch international.com} \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.$ 

food and drink industry on business and technical issues ranging from international business strategy to factory design. Zenith works with over 1000 clients, in more than 90 countries. As Country Associate, I manage projects and analyst in 5 African Countries – Nigeria, South Africa, Kenya, Angola and Ghana.

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS	
n/a	
PUBLICATIONS	
n/a	
LANGUAGES	

English